{
  "name": "miscellaneous",
  "version": 0,
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "fwnyfvsftd",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the 10 kinds of cognitive distortions?",
      "answer": "1) All or Nothing Thinking 2) Overgeneralization 3) Mental Filter 4) Disqualifying the Positive 5) Jumping to Conclusions 6) Magnification or Minimization 7) Emotional Reasoning 8) Should Statements 9) Labeling and Mislabeling 10) Personalization",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "wd61yvremm",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "Attractive people have it easier in life.",
      "answer": "\"- you cannot cleanly divide the world into \"\"attractive people\"\" and \"\"unattractive people\"\" - attractive people are just as likely to have terrible things happen to them - some parts of life will be easier for them, but other parts will be harder - even if something comes more easily, it will not feel like an accomplishment because it didn't take effort - assuming the purpose of life is to a) be happy and b) to do the things that are a part of human life (love, compete, grieve etc), being attractive has no effect on whether one is able to experience these things\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "srzlf1pa6q",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the six principles of persuasion?",
      "answer": "- reciprocity  - commitment and consistency  - social proof - liking - authority - scarcity",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "bj9t0otbcu",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is each chapter in part I of Feeling Good about?",
      "answer": "1) Introduction to CBT 2) Self-diagnosis 3) Idea that thoughts influence emotions; intro to cognitive distortions",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "mwl87zv0gw",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the five chapters in part II of Feeling Good?",
      "answer": "4) techniques for building self-esteem 5) techniques for motivating oneself, and common mindsets of do-nothingism 6) techniques for maintaining self-esteem under criticism 7) techniques for dealing with anger/irritability 8) techniques for dealing with guilt",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "t5gob0mynn",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is part III of Feeling Good about?",
      "answer": "\"9) the fallacy of a \"\"realistic depression\"\"\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "3qjks7i9gi",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the five chapters in part IV of Feeling Good about?",
      "answer": "\"10) how to identify \"\"silent assumptions\"\" and correct them 11) approval 12) love 13) work 14) perfectionism\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "lqnyhu8gw4",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is part V of Feeling Good about?",
      "answer": "15) notes on suicide",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "mi0kna9rkr",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is part VI of Feeling Good about?",
      "answer": "16) how Dr. Burns applies this knowledge to his practice",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "lwbn3neh74",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is part VII of Feeling Good about?",
      "answer": "drugs, out of date though.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "hwlcs2sn8k",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are 13 common mindsets of do-nothingism?",
      "answer": "1) hopelessness 2) helplessness 3) overwhelming yourself 4) jumping to conclusions 5) self-labeling 6) undervaluing the rewards 7) perfectionism 8) fear of failure 9) fear of success 10) fear of disapproval or criticism 11) coercion and resentment 12) low frustration tolerance 13) guilt and self-blame",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "vtoudsy9ov",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the five points to remember about the pomodoro technique?",
      "answer": "- write the task down, set a timer for 25 minutes, and work on that task until finished or the timer rings   - if interrupted, either internally or externally, mark the thought, or task, down on a sheet of paper and refocus    - once a pomodoro is completed, put a mark next to the task   - if an objective isn't completed, spend pomodoros on it until it is   - if you have fewer than four check marks, take a 5 minute break between pomodoros; if you have four, then take a 30 minute break",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "0t0ym893ie",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "If something slightly positive happened to me, what are the four cognitive distortions that could be used to turn it negative?",
      "answer": "- all or nothing thinking - minimization - disqualifying the positive - mental filter",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "e5q3u5cs7u",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the four S's of intangible assets?",
      "answer": "- scalable - synergies - spillover - sunk cost",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "wi60soqnj7",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the purpose of an intimate relationship in life?",
      "answer": "It is *not* to make you happy. Life will not be sunshine and rainbows once you're in a relationship. You'll still feel like crap sometimes. You still need to work at being happy.   What it gives you is a strong relationship with another person. It gives you the ability to count on someone. It gives you someone to share your life with. Basically, it gives you a partner in crime.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "czwtirp32t",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How are frequency, alertness/wakefulness and amplitude of brain waves related?",
      "answer": "higher frequency -\u003e lower amplitude -\u003e more alertness/wakefulness",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "dv080av7at",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "Order the 5 brain waves from lowest frequency to highest frequency. What is each brain wave typically associated with?",
      "answer": "delta -\u003e deep sleep theta -\u003e daydreaming; meditation alpha -\u003e awake, but relaxed (eyes closed) beta -\u003e awake and thinking about something gamma -\u003e deeply focused on something",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "zt6d7ujbz5",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the 5 things you must remember about disapproval?",
      "answer": "\"Remember that criticism and disapproval can only bother you if you buy into them.  1) \"\"rejection is not wildfire\"\": each person makes different judgements from the information they receive   2) \"\"it's just one person\"\": what is or is not worthy of approval or disapproval is totally subjective; each person will have their own opinion   3) \"\"people are dumb\"\": peoples' opinions are often based on irrational thinking, so it doesn't make much sense to give credence to them   4) \"\"disapproval does not reduce value\"\": disapproval results from my words or actions, since that is all the world sees; my inner value is unknown to the world, and untouched by disapproval   5) \"\"disapproval is not permanent\"\": even if someone does not like you right now, they may change their mind; you may also be able to change their mind if it is important to you\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "uv41a85ifc",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "\"Rationalize the following:   1) Someone overhears you flirting with a girl and tells you to stop \"\"harassing\"\" her   2) You just about cause a car accident and someone honks loudly at you   3) You try to talk to a girl and she calls you a creep   4) A girl's boyfriend comes up while you're flirting and asks you what you're doing\"",
      "answer": "",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "k6oeul9gxy",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the three marks of existence according to Buddhism?",
      "answer": "1) impermanence 2) unsatisfactoriness/suffering 3) non-self",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "cdvydeldj9",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "According to Shinzen Young, what are the three core skills that are trained by meditation?",
      "answer": "- concentration power - sensory clarity - equanimity",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "pvlfkdfky7",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How does Shinzen Young define equanimity?",
      "answer": "Equanimity is not just calm or even temper. It is the ability to allow sensory experiences, both internal and external, to come and go without push (suppression) or pull (holding onto it). It is a state of non-self-interference. It is all about reducing the impedance of your mental circuitry.   Equanimity is **not** suppression of feeling, apathy, or inexpressiveness. It is fully feeling the sensation and allowing it to subside naturally.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "ouy3gp7lrh",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are each of Shinzen Young's five ways? What techniques does each use?",
      "answer": "1) The way of thought and emotion 2) The way of the physical senses 3) The way of tranquility4) The way of flow 5) The way of human kindness    1-4 use noting, with the exception that absolute rest in 3 involves do nothing. 5 uses nurture positive.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "8n0s9k8kvf",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the three techniques that are used in Shinzen Young's Basic Meditation?",
      "answer": "1) Noting 2) Nurture Positive 3) Do Nothing",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "zca2nk8euo",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What five roles does each of Young's five ways play?",
      "answer": "1) General skill building exercise 2) Practical tool 3) Method of knowing yourself 4) Rooted in past traditions 5) Based on modern understanding of neuroscience",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "pbi7nddjjm",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How does the noting technique work?",
      "answer": "It involves a cycle of doing three things:   1) clearly acknowledge the presence of a sensory event 2) (optional) label the event by thinking or saying a word/phrase that describes the event 3) focus intently on the event",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "120gy1jexr",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is Theravada?",
      "answer": "A form of Buddhism found in Southeast Asia. It is thought to be the closest to the original formulations of the Buddha.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "pyoh2ok64l",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the difference between attention and awareness, according to Culadasa?",
      "answer": "Attention: - conscious process; can be directed - turns a mental object into an abstract idea, if it is not already - allows us to analyze and interpret an object - can only be applied to things that are already in awareness  Awareness: - is not controllable (for non-meditators?) - provides context for the object of attention - is more about the relationships between objects",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "nzlc361ku8",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the three ways in which attention spontaneously moves?",
      "answer": "Scanning: where you search the outer world or contents of the mind for something of interest   Getting captured: when an object, such as a thought, bodily sensation or external stimulus, suddenly captures our attention   Alternating attention: a subtler kind of scattered attention where attention flits quickly between several different objects; to non-meditators it appears that attention is simultaneously on multiple things",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "h5tfhv1swz",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the five hindrances? Explain them.",
      "answer": "worldly desire: pursuit of pleasures related to our material existence; gain-loss, pleasure-pain, fame-obscurity, praise-blame   aversion: avoidance of things that are unpleasant; involves things like judgement, rejection, denial, hatred, anger, resentment, dissatisfaction, criticism, impatience, self-accusation, and boredom   laziness and lethargy: laziness appears when the cost of an activity seems to outway the benefits; lethargy manifests as lack of energy, procrastination and low motivation   agitation due to worry and remorse: remorse for unwise, unwholesome, immoral, or illegal activities; worry about consequences of past actions, or about things you imagine might happen to you; these make it hard to focus mental resources on anything else   doubt: a biased, unconscious mental process focused on negative possible outcomes; saps our will and undermines intentions",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "5kpg80g0uz",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the three stages of distraction? Describe them.",
      "answer": "Subtle Distraction: a distraction takes up fewer moments of consciousness than the object of meditation   Gross Distraction: a distraction takes up more moments of consciousness than the object of meditation   Forgetting: the distraction captures attention and takes up all moments of consciousness; the intention to focus on the object of meditation is also forgotten",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "ap9ex88qrs",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the difference between mind-wandering and monkey mind?",
      "answer": "\"Mind-wandering is where attention goes from one thought to the next; thoughts are usually related. Another term for this is \"\"train of thought\"\".   Monkey mind is an especially agitated state where attention jumps rapidly from one thing to the next, and each thing is unrelated.\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "fip8bh629g",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How do you deal with monkey mind?",
      "answer": "You expand the scope within which attention is allowed to roam.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "yoyg8cx2to",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the state of the mind at the beginning of stage two, and what is it at the end?",
      "answer": "At the beginning, most of meditation practice is spent in mind-wandering. By the end, most of the time is spent with the object of meditation in awareness, and episodes of mind-wandering are brief.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "pk1vhujck2",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "According to Culadasa, what are the two main objectives of meditation?",
      "answer": "1) stable attention 2) mindfulness",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "ejhvzsmxxo",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How does Culadasa define mindfulness?",
      "answer": "The optimal interaction between attention and awareness.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "b9hqhuebgt",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "Explain the moments of consciousness model.",
      "answer": "Consciousness is composed of sequential freeze frames called mind moments. This is not unlike a movie or a single-core processor. Each moment of consciousness may be perceiving or non-perceiving. Perceiving moments of consciousness have two characteristics: - type (there are seven different types) - attention or awareness",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "sa1gzeuem0",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the seven different types of mind moments?",
      "answer": "- sight - hearing - smell - taste - body sense (includes touch and various body sensations) - mind sense (things like thought and emotion) - binding moments of consciousness",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "gdps3h7eqq",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "Under the Mind-System model, what is the conscious mind, and what is its purpose?",
      "answer": "The conscious mind is like a computer bus that sub-minds can put selected information on, and that sub-minds can read information from. Its purpose is to connect the unconscious sub-minds.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "win8d8t666",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "Under the Mind-System model, what are the two parts of the unconscious mind, and what are their purposes?",
      "answer": "1) The Sensory Mind: contains the sub-minds that are responsible for the senses. Processes raw sensory data and recognizes, categorizes, analyzes and evaluates it in terms if its immediate importance.   2) The Discriminating Mind: contains the sub-minds associated with the mind sense (thinking and emotional minds) and binding moments of consciousness (narrating mind). Gets access to all sensations from the sensory mind, whether or not they were projected into consciousness. Forms sensations into perceptions.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "s9nvg1gus2",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "In TMI, what is the goal of stage three? How is this accomplished?",
      "answer": "The goal of stage three is to eliminate forgetting.   Most importantly, stable attention must be developed through following and maybe connecting. This allows you to better detect distractions without being swept away by them. Also, introspective awareness is developed through labeling and checking in. Finally, peripheral awareness should be maintained.   Remember, we aren't trying to have exclusive attention on the breath - that's impossible at this stage. You can expect to have the following mind moments, all of which are ok as long as attention remains in the breath:   - following the breath - non-perceiving mind moments - moments of peripheral awareness  - moments of checking in - moments of labeling - gross/subtle distractions",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "cspj26tx9z",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "List all of the poker hands, top-ranked to low-ranked.",
      "answer": "1) five of a kind: four of a kind plus a wild card (joker) 2) straight flush: a flush, all of the same suit 3) four of a kind: four cards of one rank and one card of another rank 4) full house: three cards of one rank and two of another rank 5) flush: five cards of the same suit, but not sequential rank 6) straight: five cards of sequential rank, but different suits 7) three of a kind: three cards of one rank and two cards of other ranks 8) two pair: two cards of one rank, two cards of another rank and one card of a third rank 9) one pair: two cards of one rank and three cards of three other ranks 10) high card: nothing",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "lxs7fm9hxy",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are the four actions you can take when betting in poker?",
      "answer": "fold: lose whatever you have bet and exit the round   call: match whatever the bet has been raised to   check: decline to raise or fold (not an option in 1st round of betting)   raise: increase the bet by at least 2x current bet; followed by another round of betting until it gets to you again",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "30y3n9hx0o",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "In Texas hold 'em, what are the names for each of the three card reveals?",
      "answer": "flop: refers to the three cards that are laid face up after the first round of betting  turn: the 4th card that is laid face up after the second round of betting  river: the 5th card that is laid face up after the third round of betting",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "zs8rov7gnk",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the standard for international phone numbers called? What standards body wrote it? How does it work?",
      "answer": "E.164 ITU-T   Format is [+][country_code][number]   According to the standard you have to use +, but in practice 00 may work. Country code may be 1-3 digits, and has the value 1 for Canada and the US.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "dd1kzyoyvp",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How is betting started in a hand of texas hold 'em?",
      "answer": "The blind is set at the table. Big blind is 2x little blind. Little blind is the bet by the person to the left of the dealer, and big blind is the bet for everyone else if nobody raises.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "le6jurld4z",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the difference between transitive and intransitive verbs? Give an example for each.",
      "answer": "\"transitive: must exert an action on an object: \"\"please bring coffee\"\" \"\"I conveyed the message\"\"    intransitive: does not require an object to act upon: \"\"they jumped\"\" \"\"a light was shining\"\"\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "10jvvlry7j",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the difference between subject, direct object and indirect object?",
      "answer": "\"subject: the noun or pronoun that performs the verb in a sentence chris in \"\"chris ate cereal\"\"  direct object: the thing that is acted upon cereal in \"\"chris ate cereal\"\"  indirect object: recipient  \"\"Althea threw me a frisbee\"\" subject: Althea direct object: frisbee indirect object: me  \"\"Wanda gave Louie a gift card\"\" subject: Wanda direct object: gift card indirect object: Louie\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "q7ke311qof",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "horticulture: in fertilizers, what do the three numbers x-y-z mean? What does each part of this help the plant develop?",
      "answer": "NPK   Each number is the percent of the mixture that is comprised of that element.  x: nitrogen - general health - vegetative growth   y: phosphorus - used more during blooming - important for healthy roots   z: potassium - general health  - disease resistance",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "zjd7i19w5r",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is lacquer?",
      "answer": "\"\"\"Lacquer\"\" refers to a one of two hard finishes applied to materials such as wood or metal:   1) Asian lacquerware (\"\"true lacquer\"\"), which is made with treated, dyed and dried sap of certain trees. Produces a hard, smooth, durable, waterproof finish.   2) Really any kind of polymer, clear or pigmented, dissolved in lacquer thinner, which is a mixture of a number of solvents. This is what you get if you buy lacquer today.\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "elom0pq3lg",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is shellac?",
      "answer": "A resious secretion of the Indian/Southeast Asian lac insect. Is dissolved in denatured alcohol and used to finish wood. Not to be confused with lacquer.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "rxl6su4v3g",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is varnish?",
      "answer": "Anything really. It may be similar to a lacquer, or may use drying oils, or curing, or anything. It's just a finish - read the back of the can to understand what to expect from it.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "47btsxrmn4",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is polyurethane?",
      "answer": "It is what I think of as Varathane. It takes a while to dry and needs multiple (~3) coats.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "xf6xuqd7oa",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is phototropism?",
      "answer": "It is the tendency of plants to grow towards light. It is dependent on the tip of the sprout seeing light - it then produces hormones that go down to the shaded side of the plant and cause accelerated growth.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "da5r43cxjn",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is photoperiod?",
      "answer": "It is advantageous for plants to behave differently at different times of the year/season. Photoperiod refers to the way a plant changes its behaviour in response to long/short days/nights. This mechanism works differently for every species of plants. Usually it affects things like when the plant flowers, or when it starts to devote energy to growing a bulb.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "4v7jax4tgw",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is denatured alcohol? What is its other name?",
      "answer": "It is ethanol that has additives to discourage people from drinking it recreationally. It is also known as methylated spirits.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "f9gzx8anur",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What are mineral spirits? What are alternative names for it?",
      "answer": "\"Mineral spirits are a common solvent used in painting, and degreasing machine tools/parts. The word \"\"mineral\"\" is meant to distinguish it from distilled spirits such as those containing ethanol. Often used as a cheaper substitute for turpentine, though it is not as good of a solvent.   Also known as white spirit (UK), mineral turpentine (AU/NZ), turpentine substitute, petroleum spirits, and paint thinner (though technically paint thinner is a broader category).\"",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "ygmvkacdtq",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 1 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- polyethylene terephthalate (PETE) - generally used for single-use applications - does leach some chemicals - best to avoid and don't reuse it - not very easy to recycle; requires nasty chemicals",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "c1yy8ogf6n",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 2 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- high-density polyethylene (HDPE) - resistant to sunlight and temperature extremes  - safe for reuse - easily recycled",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "at0pnbmaov",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 3 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- polyvinyl chloride (PVC) - resistant to sunlight and temperature extremes - leaches nasty chemicals throughout life cycle; not safe for reuse - not recyclable",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "m6997y46wl",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 4 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- low-density polyethylene - more flexible than HDPE - relatively safe to reuse",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "cianw6ksx2",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 5 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- polypropylene (PP) - considered safe for reuse",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "37v1lfk6eg",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 6 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- polystyrene (PS) - difficult to recycle, breaks up and ends up in marine animals - not suitable for reuse; leaches chemicals",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "jsmdzd90ze",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What does plastic symbol 7 represent? Is it safe for reuse?",
      "answer": "- other (acrylic, nylon, polycarbonate, polylactic acid (PLA)) - better to assume it is not reusable",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "8n32rn7z3i",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is the difference between LDPE and HDPE?",
      "answer": "Both are polymers of ethylene. Both have long chains of polymers. However, LDPE has branches that go off of the chains, whereas HDPE has only long chains. This means that LDPE is less dense, but more ductile, whereas HDPE is more dense and robust.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "g55gh84tey",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "In meditation, how is forgetting defined?",
      "answer": "Forgetting is where: - attention is no longer on the object of meditation - the object of meditation is not in awareness - the intention to keep attention on the object of meditation is forgotten   This is another way of saying that no mind moments go towards the object of meditation.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "s817jpp4hu",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How big is a hectare?",
      "answer": "100m by 100m, or 10 000 m^2.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "xeclyxown9",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How big is an acre in feet? How big is an acre in metres?",
      "answer": "66 feet by 660 feet 4047 m^2",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "6t4it8ifkt",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What direction do range roads run in Alberta? In what direction do their numbers increase?",
      "answer": "Range roads run north to south. Their numbers increase as you go west.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "qu4pmkqy4e",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What direction do township roads run? In what direction do their numbers increase?",
      "answer": "Township roads run east-west, and their numbers increase as you go north.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "yyqet0ui56",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is a township?",
      "answer": "A township is a 6 mile by 6 mile square.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "rmpbvyt85t",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "What is a section?",
      "answer": "A section is a 1 mile by 1 mile square.",
      "reviews": []
    },
    {
      "id": "vb4aeqab22",
      "version": 0,
      "active": true,
      "question": "How many grams are in one ounce?",
      "answer": "28 grams",
      "reviews": []
    }
  ]
}